chaptercheats.com 2010-04-22

# Privacy Policy

**Agreement:**  
By using our website, you state that you understand the following policies and agree to abide by all rules stated. You also understand policies regarding your own personal details.

**Personal Details:**  
At some point you may be asked for certain details, such as your email address, in order to register for specific facilities on our website.

As a result of entering your details, you will never receive so-called "junkmail" or "spam", as we do not pass your details on to any other third-party.

The details you will be asked for are simply required to ensure people do not register for facilities on our website with no intention of using them.

**Copyright:**  
The website design is our property - therefore graphics can not be taken from here and reproduced in any way whatsoever without written permission from one of our administrators.

Email: admin[at]chaptercheats[dot]com

Also note that we are in no way affiliated or associated with [Microsoft Coporation](http://www.microsoft.com/).

**Chaptercheats.com**  
does not sell, rent, lease or allow any third parties to view or use the information collected unless the reader consents through the use of the site, or in any other way. Chaptercheats.com site does not send unsolicited emails.

**Chaptercheats.com**  
takes reasonable measures to keep the information disclosed secure. However, Chaptercheats.com assumes no responsibility for any breach of security to this data.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. Chaptercheats.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites, or their content.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Chaptercheats.com uses cookies to enhance the user's experience, often allowing a user to browse the site more quickly. The storage of such cookie is optional, and the user will still be able to use the website, with the exception of our member's area which requires a cookie to determine a member's login status. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Third Party Advertising**  
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by Third Party Advertising. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. For more information about Third Party Advertising, and cookies, please [Click Here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp)

Chaptercheats.com uses Gorilla Nation, Valueclick, and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. This is a feature known as online behavioral advertising ("OBA") and/or multi-site advertising. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>. 

**ValueClick**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org. 

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this "behavioral advertising" practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit <http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>

**Adtegrity.com**  
Chaptercheats.com uses the services of Adtegrity.com, LLC for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To learn more about Adtegrity.com, including how to opt out of their third party advertising, go to: [http://www.adtegrity.com/about/privacy-policy/](http://www.adtegrity.com/privacy.asp).

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**Note:**  
This privacy policy is subject to change at any time, without any given notice.

© 1999-2010,
